layyous.com 2012-12-31

# Privacy Statement for Layyous.com policies we have put into place to safeguard your privacy

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

Dr Najeeb Layyous is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy as a visitor to his Web site at http://www.layyous.com. We take the issue of privacy very seriously and value the trust you place in us each time you use our services and access this Web site. This Privacy Statement describes the practices and policies we have put into place to safeguard your personal and health-related personal information that may be gathered and used as you visit our Web site. 

THIS NOTICE DESCRIBES HOW MEDICAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU MAY BE USED AND DISCLOSED AND HOW YOU CAN GET ACCESS TO THIS INFORMATION. PLEASE REVIEW IT CAREFULL.

The policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. If you have any questions about our privacy policies, we encourage you to contact us using any of the methods outlined at the end of our Privacy Statement.

**Who Is Collecting the Information?**

Dr Najeeb Layyous is collecting information on this Web site as outlined in this privacy statement.

**What Information Do We Collect? and how do we use it?**

_Automatic Collection of Information:_  
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the web site or download information, our system will automatically gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and is used in an aggregate way to help us improve our web site and tell us the number of visitors to our site each day. 

_Permission-based Collection of Information:_  
At different places on our site depending upon the feature you use, you may be asked to volunteer personal and health-related information such as your name, email, mailing address, telephone number, and health history. 

**With Whom Will the Information Be Shared?**

The personally identifiable information gathered during your visit to this Web site is not shared with any organization for any purpose. 

Dr Najeeb Layyous has the right to reveal the personally, identifiable information for website visitors in cases which involves legal issues to defend himself and his website or a user of the website.

**Access and Correction of Personal Information**

_Review of Personal Information_  
Site visitors may not access information we have collected and maintain about them 

_Use of our forum and other public places in our website._

Dr Najeeb Layyous site contains infertility and endoscopey public forum. the information submitted in this forum is public and its privacy cannot be controlled . so any information that you submit in the forum is public and you are warned not to submit private information.

**Our Use of Cookies**

We do not use any cookies to store or collect information on our Web site.

**Registration for Access**

Visitors can use this entire Web site anonymously, without registration.

**Family safe site**

We are especially concerned about protecting children's privacy. We hope parents and teachers are involved in children's Internet explorations. It is particularly important for parents to guide their children when children are asked to provide personal information on line. 

Dr Najeeb Layyous site is an educational site containing information about infertility, male and female genital system's anatomy and information about pregnancy and delivery, which are within the limits put in any educational school program . however Dr Najeeb Layyous stresses that it is up to the parents to decide which age group from their family is allowed to visit his site, as concepts and beliefs vary amongst different families.

**Security of Communications**

We recognize that many people are concerned about the privacy and protection of information as it is transmitted over the Internet. You should keep in mind that the possibility exists for unauthorized individuals to intercept any email message you send over the Internet. 

We use e-mail forms and consultation forms to allow our visitors to ask questions about our services, available treatments and ask for free consultation. These are not hosted on a secure server. The possibility exists that unauthorized individuals may intercept email messages.

**E-commerce and On-line Donations**

Purchasing items or making donations over the Internet usually requires you to provide your personal identifying information and credit card information on a Web site. Many people have become accustomed to on-line commerce as a time-saving and useful convenience. There are a number of practices that can make providing your sensitive credit card information more secure and therefore make you feel more comfortable about doing so. 

At this time, we do not process credit card payments for donations, or advertising on our Web site.

**Advertising Servers**

On-line advertising, such as banner ads, has become commonplace on many Web sites. Certain Web sites have developed relationships with third-party advertising servers to display these advertisements on their sites. By clicking on one of these banner ads, you will be taken to another site with different privacy policies. These third party ad servers may also use cookies to collect non-personal information on your preferences and interests via the advertisement you decide to view. 

we encourage users to review the privacy policy of each advertising company as we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of these sites.

**Links to Other Sites**

Web sites often provide a number of links that offer direct access to other useful or interesting web sites holding potential value to site visitors. Inclusion of the other sites by links does not imply any endorsement of the material or information on the other sites. Users are encouraged to review the privacy policy of each linked site before sharing personal and health-related information.

This site includes links to non-affiliated external Web sites. We have the following practices:

  * We encourage users to review the privacy policy of each linked site, as we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of other sites.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we  will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

**Web Site Contact Information**

If you have questions about our privacy policy, or feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, please contact us.

Contact: Dr Najeeb Layyous F.R.C.O.G  
Tel: clinic    96265656575  
Fax: 96265655293  
P.O.Box 830038,Amman 11183,Jordan  
e-mail: [layyous@layyous.com](mailto:layyous@layyous.com)  

**Modification Date**

This privacy statement was last modified on September 4, 2003.
